As long as you love me
Although loneliness has always
been a friend of mine
I am leavin′ my life in your hands
People say I am crazy
and that I am blind
Risking it all in a glance
And how you got me blind
is still a mystery
I can′t get you out of my head
Don′t care what is written
in your history
As long as You are here with me
I don′t care who you are
Where You are from
What you did
As long as you love me
Who you are
Where You are from
Don′t care what you did
As long as you love me
Every little thing that
you have said and done
Feels like It is deep within me
Doesn′t really matter if
You are on the run
It seems like We are meant to be
I don′t care who you are (who you are)
Where You are from (where
You are from)
What you did
As long as you love me (I don′t know)
Who you are (who you are)
Where You are from (where
You are from)
Don′t care what you did
As long as you love me
I have tried to hide it
so that no one knows
But I guess it shows
When you look into my eyes
What you did and where
You are comin from
I don′t care‚ as long
as you love me‚ baby
I don′t care who you are (who you are)
Where You are from (where
You are from)
What you did
As long as you love me (as
long as you love me)
Who you are (who you are)
Where You are from (where
You are from)
Don′t care what you did
As long as you love me (as
long as you love me)
Who you are (who you are)
Where You are from
What you did
As long as you love me
Who you are (who you are)
Where You are from (where
You are from)
As long as you love me
Who you are
What you did (I don′t care)
As long as you love me
www.RentAnAdviser.com